Seduction. Sex. Scandal.
A Good Woman is a comedy, romance film directed by Mike Barker.
Fleeing 1930s New York and leaving behind a chequered past, the giltzy divorcee
Mrs Stella Erlynne travels to Italy's sun-dappled Amalfi coast.
Mrs Erlynne's appearance causes a stir amongst the visiting aristocracy.
Based on the Oscar Wilde play "Lady Windemere's Fan."
Stella Erlynne, played by Helen Hunt.
Meg Windermere, played by Scarlett Johansson.
Tuppy, played by Tom Wilkinson.
Lord Darlington, played by Stephen Campbell Moore.
Robert Windemere, played by Mark Umbers.
Contessa Lucchino, played by Milena Vukotić.
A Good Woman is a 2004 romantic comedy drama film directed by Mike Barker.
The screenplay by Howard Himelstein is based on the 1892
play Lady Windermere's Fan by Oscar Wilde.
It is the fourth screen version of the work, following a 1916 silent film using Wilde's original title,
Ernst Lubitsch's 1925 version, and Otto Preminger's 1949 adaptation entitled The Fan.
The film explores themes of italy, based on play or
musical, love affair, gossip, newlywed.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.